Reg Manning Papers
Reg Manning Papers
- Published material
  - From Tee to Cup illustrations, 1954; with note of explanation from Manning (Box 1)
Argentina B3 B9 B12 B19 B21 B25-B26
Arizona National Guard B2 B4 B8 B11 B17 B20
Arizona State Legislature B2-B3 B5 B8 B11 B14 B17 B20 B23 B26
Arkansas B9-B10
armed forces B1-B2 B4-B9 B11 B13-B16 B17-B22 B24 B26
arts and culture B20
Ashurst, Henry B20
Asia B3-B5 B12 B15-B17 B26
Atlantic Pact B1
Attlee, Clement B2 B4
Australia B5 B9
Austria B4-B5
auto industry B7 B9-B10
automation B12 B21 B26
aviation B4-B6 B8-B9 B11
Baker, Bobby B26
bakers' union B7-B8
banking industry B5-B6
Batista, Fulgencio B7 B9
Bay of Pigs invasion B18 B24
Beck, Dave B6-B7
Belgium B14 B17-B18
Ben Bella, Ahmed B22 B24-B25
Benson, Ezra Taft B6 B8-B9 B15-B16
Berlin Wall B21-B22 B26
birth control B24
black market B2
Bowles, Chester B16 B19-B20 B22
Brandt, Willy B18-B19
Brazil B18-B21 B25
Britain B1-B14 B17-B19 B21-B26
Brown Sr., Edmund Gerald "Pat" B10 B12-B14 B18-B19 B22
Bulganin, Nikolai B4-B9
Bunche, Ralph B1 B24
business B2 B5 B9-B10 B11 B18-B22 B25
Butler, Paul M. B10-B11 B15
Byrd, Robert B8
California B1-B2 B4-B7 B9 B14 B16-B17 B19 B22-B24 B26
Cambodia B26
Canada B6-B7 B9 B12 B16 B21 B24-B26
capitalism B1 B7 B12-B13 B26
Castro, Fidel B11-B26
Castro, Raul B16 B24
censorship B10 B18-B19
census B14-B15 B17 B20
charity B3-B4 B14 B17 B20 B23
children B1 B7 B12 B21
Chile B15
China B1-B4 B6-B7 B9-B26
Churchill, Winston B1-B4
cities B16
civil defense B19
civil rights B4 B7 B14-B15 B18 B20 B22-B23 B25-B26
coal industry B1 B24
Cold War B2 B4 B6 B10 B14-B16 B26
college students B6 B8 B13 B15 B19 B26
colonialism B19 B26
Colorado River B1-B5 B8 B14 B17 B20 B23
Columbus, Christopher B3 B7 B10 B16 B22 B25
common market B19-B20 B22-B25
communism B1-B7 B9-B21 B23-B26
Congo B15-B19 B21 B23-B24
Congress B1-B26
construction industry B11 B14 B20 B23
consumers B5 B8 B17-B18
Cormier, Lucia B16
corruption B2-B3 B11
crime B3-B8 B12 B14 B16 B19-B21 B23 B25-B26
Cuba B6-B7 B9 B11-B17 B19-B26
Cyprus B4 B9-B10 B26
Czechoslovakia B21 B24
de Gaulle, Charles B9-B26
democracy B2 B12 B14
Democratic Party B1-B26
demonstrations B15 B25-B26
demonstrations B10 B19 B25-B26
Diem, Ngo Dinh B25
Dirksen, Everett B14 B18 B20 B22
disarmament B6-B7 B10 B13 B15 B21
Dominican Republic B11 B13 B18 B20 B24
Dulles, John Foster B3-B12
economy B1 B6 B9 B18-B19
Ecuador B25
Eden, Anthony B3 B5
education B3 B7-B8 B10-B11 B17-B19 B25
Egypt B1-B6 B8 B19
Eichmann, Adolf B18
Eisenhower, Dwight B1-B18 B20-B22 B25-B26
Eisenhower, Milton B18
elderly B4 B16
elections B10 B12 B15-B17 B19-B20 B22-B23 B25-B26
electricity needs B17 B23
En-lai, Chou B6 B26
Erhard, Ludwig B24 B26
espionage B1 B6 B16 B21
Estes, Billie Sol B4-B5 B22
Europe B1-B3 B6 B17 B24 B26
Fannin, Paul B14 B16-B17 B20 B23 B26
farming B6 B9-B13 B15-B19 B21-B26
fashion B17
Federal Bureau of Investigation B7
Federal Communications Commission B9 B12
Food and Drug Administration B22
foreign aid B6 B8-B9 B12-B14 B16-B17 B19 B21 B23-B26
foreign policy B2-B3 B7 B15 B17-B19 B24 B26
forest fires B9 B11 B17 B20 B23
Formosa B2-B3 B8 B10 B16
France B2-B14 B16 B18-B19 B21-B22 B26
Franco, Francisco B2 B8 B26
freedom B2 B4 B8-B9 B12 B15 B18
freedom of the press B11 B15-B16 B19 B23 B25
Freeman, Orville B18-B19 B22 B24-B25
Frondizi, Arturo B12 B21
Fulbright, J. William B19 B24-B26
Germany B1-B4 B7-B16 B18-B22 B25
Glenn, John B20-B21 B26
Goddard, Sam B20
gold reserve B16 B25
Goldwater, Barry B3-B4 B10-B11 B17-B21 B23-B26
Gomulka, Władysław B9-B10 B22
Goulart, João B20-B21
government (in general) B1-B2 B6 B9 B12 B14-B15 B19-B24 B26
government spending B10 B18-B21 B23-B26
graduates B1 B3-B4 B9 B18 B21 B24
Greece B1 B4 B9-B10 B26
Gromyko, Andrei B6-B7 B9 B12 B15 B18-B19 B22 B25
Guantanamo B15 B17 B26
Guatemala B3
Guevara, Che B14-B16
Guinea B17
Haiti B24
Halleck, Charles B18
Hammarskjold, Dag B10 B16-B19
Harriman, W. Averell B4 B10 B18-B19 B25-B26
Hawaii B5 B9 B11-B12
Hayden, Carl B4 B6 B10 B17 B20 B22-B24 B26
healthcare B8 B11 B15 B17 B21
Herter, Christian B12-B13
Hirohito B1
Hitler, Adolf B1 B4
Hoffa, Jimmy B7 B10 B12 B18-B20 B25-B26
holidays B1-B6 B8 B10-B20 B23-B26
Hoover, Hebert B17 B20
House Un-American Activities Committee B1
housing B19-B20 B23
Hsiu Chuan, Wu B24
Humphrey, Hubert B12-B15 B19 B22 B24 B26
Hungary B1 B5-B7 B9-B10 B12 B18 B23 B25
Hussein B6
Iceland B5 B10 B12
Illinois B16
India B3-B7 B11-B14 B19-B24
Indonesia B9-B10 B14 B17
industry (general) B1 B10 B12 B17 B19-B21 B24
inflation B2-B3 B6-B7 B9-B10 B12 B21-B22
integration B4-B7 B9-B10 B14 B24
Iran B2-B3 B10
Iraq B5 B8 B10-B12 B18 B24
Israel B1 B4 B6 B10-B11 B14 B18-B19 B24-B25
Italy B7 B11 B15 B24-B25
Japan B1-B3 B6-B7 B19 B21
John Birch Society B18 B25
Johnson, Lyndon Baines B10-B19 B22 B26
Jordan B6-B9 B24
journalism B1 B3 B10 B13 B16 B18-B19 B22-B25
judicial system B2-B3 B14 B17 B26
justice B8 B14
juvenile delinquency B2 B4-B6 B8 B13 B26
Kai-shek, Chiang B2-B3 B10
Qasim, Abd al-Karim (Kassem) B11-B12 B19
Kefauver, Estes B4 B14
Kennedy, Caroline B24
Kennedy, Jacqueline B17 B24-B25
Kennedy, John F. B7 B11-B26
Kennedy, Joseph P. B16
Kennedy, Robert F. B16 B18-B19 B22 B24-B26
Kennedy, Ted B16 B21-B22
Khedda, Ben B22
Khrushchev, Nikita B4-B26
King Saud of Saudi Arabia B6
Knight, Goodwin B6-B7 B10 B19
Knowland, William B6-B7 B9-B10
Korea B7 B15 B22 B25
Korean War B2-B3
Kuwait B18-B19
labor B9 B12 B16 B21
Laos B13 B16 B18 B21-B22 B24-B25
Latin America B3 B6 B8 B13-B14 B16-B19 B21-B26
Lebanon B9
left-wing extremists B25
Lewis, John B1-B2
liberty B2 B7
Lilienthal, David E. B1
Lincoln, Abraham B1 B11
Little Rock B9-B10
Lodge Jr., Henry Cabot B16 B26
Lodge, George C. B22
Long, Earl B12
Lumumba, Patrice B16-B17
MacArthur, Douglas B2 B19 B26
MacMillan, Harold B6 B9-B13 B15 B17-B18 B20-B25
Makarios III B26
Malaysia B25
Malenkov, Georgy B3-B4
Malinovsky, Rodion B15
Mansfield, Mike B19 B22
Marshall Plan B1
Massachusetts B21-B23
Mateos, Adolfo López B11
Matheson, Mac B17
McCarthy, Joseph B3-B4
McCormacK, Eddie B21-B22
McCormack, John B20-B22 B26
McFarland, Ernest B3-B5 B8
McNamara, Robert B12 B22-B24 B26
Meany, George B11 B19 B22 B26
Medicare B20-B23
Menon, Krishna B22-B23
Mexico B1 B3 B20 B22 B26
Middle East B2-B7 B9-B12 B14 B19 B22 B25
Mikoyan, Anastas B11 B14 B19
Mills, Wilbur B22
mining B18
Mississippi B22 B26
Molotov, Vyacheslav B3-B4 B6-B7 B10 B21
Mongolia B7
Monroe Doctrine B15
morality B21
Morocco B8 B25
Morse, Wayne B12 B14-B15 B22 B26
Murrow, Edward R. B17
Mussolini, Benito B1 B4
Nasser, Gamal Abdel B4-B7 B9-B14 B17-B19 B23-B24
national debt B1 B3 B7 B17-B18 B22-B26
nationalism B2 B11-B12
NATO B3-B6 B8-B14 B22-B24 B26
natural disasters B2 B12 B15 B26
nature B4-B5 B8 B11 B20 B25
Nazism B14 B18
Nehru, Jawaharlal B3-B5 B12-B14 B18 B20-B23
Nepal B13
neutrality B4 B13 B18-B19 B21
New Deal B1
New Guinea B21
New York (State) B10-B11 B23-B24 B26
New York City B8 B17 B19 B24 B26
Nhu, Ngo Dinh B25
Nixon, Pat B3
Nixon, Richard M. B3 B5-B16 B18-B19 B22 B24-B26
North Borneo B26
nuclear weapons B1-B7 B9-B10 B12-B15 B18-B26
oil B2 B5-B11 B18 B26
Olympics B5 B26
organized crime B7 B9 B22
Oswald, Lee Harvey B26
pacifism B9 B17
Pakistan B10 B13 B19 B21-B23 B26
Palestine B1 B24
Panama B12 B26
Panama Canal B14 B26
peace B1-B2 B5-B6 B9 B12 B18 B21-B22 B25
Peace Corps B19 B24
Pennsylvania B8-B9 B22
Peron, Juan Domingo B3-B4 B9 B25
Peru B9
Petkov, Nikola B1
Philippines B9 B11 B19 B22
Poland B4-B7 B9 B21 B24
police B8 B24
polio B17
politicians B4 B13 B15
pollution B3 B8 B20 B23 B26
population B4 B6 B11 B14 B17 B20 B23-B24
Portugal B20
Presley, Elvis B6
prisons B8
Proxmire, William B11-B12
Pyle, John Howard B3
Quadros, Jânio B18-B19 B21
quiz shows B11 B13
race B16
racism B7 B12 B15
railroad industry B13 B22 B25-B26
Rayburn, Sam B10-B11 B13-B20
religion B15-B16
Republican Party B1-B26
Reuther, Walter B8 B10-B11 B13 B16 B18 B26
Ribicoff, Abraham B21-B22
right to work law B4 B7-B9
right-wing extremists B25
Rockefeller, Nelson B10-B15 B17 B19 B23-B26
Romney, George W. B22-B23 B25
Roosevelt, Eleanor B15 B18
Roosevelt, Theodore B9-B10 B17-B18
Rusk, Dean B17-B19 B21-B22 B24-B26
Russia B1-B26
Ruth, Babe B19
Salt River B8 B20 B23
Saudi Arabia B10 B18 B24
savings bonds B6
schools B2 B5-B11 B14 B19-B20 B23 B25-B26
science B4 B8 B10 B12
Scranton, William B23 B26
Searles, Dick B8
SEATO B9 B18
secrecy B12 B15
segregation B7
Senner, George F. B23-B24
Shepilov, Dmitri B5-B6
shipping industry B1 B12 B19
Shriver, Sargent B26
Sihanouk, Norodom B26
Smith, Margaret Chase B16 B26
social security B17 B19 B21-B22
socialism B2 B7 B11 B19 B21-B22
South America B9-B16 B18-B19
Soviet Union B6-B7 B9 B12-B13 B15-B16 B18 B20-B22 B24 B26
space exploration B6-B10 B12-B13 B16 B18-B23 B25-B26
Spain B14 B26
sports B4 B6-B10 B13-B14 B16-B17 B19-B20 B22-B25
Sputnik B7-B8
Stalin, Joseph B1-B7 B19-B22
Stassen, Harold B6-B10 B26
state fair B4-B5 B11 B17 B20
steel industry B1 B3 B7 B10 B12-B14 B19 B21 B24
Stevenson, Adlai E. B3-B5 B7-B8 B12-B15 B17-B19 B23 B26
stock market B6-B7
strikes B1 B4 B7 B10-B13 B18-B21 B24-B26
students B6 B10 B18 B23
Sudan B9
Suez Canal B2-B3 B5-B6
Sukarno B9 B21 B26
Supreme Court B7 B10-B11 B18 B23-B24 B26
Symington, Stuart B12-B15
Syria B5 B7-B9 B19 B24
Taft Hartley Act B1 B11 B19
Taft, Robert B2-B3
Tanganyika B26
taxes B1-B3 B5-B26
Teamsters B6-B7 B10 B19
technology B26
telephone industry B4
television B9
terrorism B21-B22
Texas B3 B9 B16 B21 B24
Thailand B21
Thant, U. B22-B26
Tibet B11-B13 B18
Tito, Josip Broz B1 B4-B7 B9 B11-B13 B16 B22-B25
tourism B3 B9 B13-B15
trade B3 B5-B7 B9-B10 B12-B14 B16 B21 B25-B26
traffic fatalities B1-B12 B14-B20 B22-B23 B26
transportation B3 B5 B7 B9 B11-B14 B17 B20 B22-B23 B26
Trujillo, Rafael B11-B13
Truman, Harry S. B1-B5 B7-B8 B10 B14-B17 B20
Tshombe, Moise B24
Tunisia B8-B9 B19
Turkey B4-B7 B9-B10 B15 B26
U.S. Constitution B2-B3 B7
U.S. Flag B2 B4 B9 B12 B22 B25
U.S. Postal Service B2 B6-B10 B13 B15 B19 B21 B23 B25
Udall, Stewart B14 B16-B18 B20 B23-B24
Ulbricht, Walter B19 B25-B26
unemployment B8-B10 B16-B19 B22 B26
unions B1 B3 B6-B13 B16 B21-B22 B24-B25
United Arab Republic B17-B19 B24
United Arab Republic B17-B19
United Auto Workers B9
United Nations B1-B10 B14-B26
universities B8 B11 B20
urban affairs and housing B21
utility bills B9
Vandenberg, Arthur B1 B4
Venezuela B9 B25
Vietnam War B25-B26
Vishinsky, Andrey B1
voting B3 B5 B8 B10 B13-B16 B18 B20 B23-B24
Wagner, Jr., Robert F. B17
Wallace, Henry B1
war B2 B9 B12 B15 B22
War on Poverty B26
Warren, Earl B3 B11 B18
Washington D.C. B18 B25
Washington, George B3 B8 B14 B17 B24
water safety B7
water shortage B1-B5 B8 B14 B17 B20 B23 B26
weather B1-B2 B4-B6 B8-B9 B11 B14 B17 B20-B21 B23-B25
Wilson, Harold B4 B7 B24-B25
World War II B1 B4 B10 B12 B16 B18 B22 B25
World's Fair B9
Yalta B1-B2
Yates, Sidney R. B22
Yemen B23-B24
Yugoslavia B1 B7 B9 B21
Zanzibar B26
Zedong, Mao B3 B9-B13 B15-B18 B20 B22-B26
Zhukov, Marshal B7
Zorin, Valerian B21